seoimage.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - SEO Image | Reputation Management & NYC SEO Company

SEO Image, Inc. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://seoimage.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  *    “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
  *    “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  *    “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
  *    “Analytics” We use third party analytics tools that provide us visitor tracking information including the time spent on a page, clicked pages, the number of pages you visit, referring websites, search terms used to find us, where you exit the website, and we track actions of filling out forms or using tools. Our tools do not track you.

Additionally, when you fill out a form to request service information or a free website SEO audit, we collect certain information from you, including your name, company, phone number, email address, and any additional information you submit. We refer to this information as “Contact Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Contact Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Contact Information that we collect generally to fulfill any service requests for information placed throughout the Site. Additionally, we use this Contact Information to:

Communicate with you;  
Develop a proposal for marketing or design services.

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

We may use some of this data with third party advertising to present remarketing advertisements to you on third party sites after you have left our site.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, We Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising here:  
FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an contact through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION

When you place a contact through the Site, we will maintain your Contact Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at seo (at) seoimage.com or by mail using the details provided below:

155 E 57th St, 11 FL, New York, NY, 10022, United States
